{
    "SAP": {
        "basic": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "What is SAP?",
                "options": [
                    "Services Applications and Products",
                    "Systems Applications and Products",
                    "Systems Applications and Processes",
                    "Services Applications and Processes"
                ],
                "answer": "Systems Applications and Products"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "Which business unit does SAP belongs to?",
                "options": [
                    "DX",
                    "DNA",
                    "EAS",
                    "IVS"
                ],
                "answer": "EAS"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "What is the primary programming language to create a SAP application?",
                "options": [
                    "Java",
                    "C#",
                    "C++",
                    "ABAP"
                ],
                "answer": "ABAP"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "What is SAP Fiori?",
                "options": [
                    "SAP's database",
                    "SAP's user experience",
                    "SAP's ERP Module"
                ],
                "answer": "SAP's user experiance"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "What is SAP's in memory database?",
                "options": [
                    "SAP Hana",
                    "SAP Fiori",
                    "SAP Oracle",
                    "SAP SoH"
                ],
                "answer": "SAP Hana"
            }
        ],
        "medium": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "ABAP programs are developed and executed on which layer?",
                "options": [
                    "Presentation layer",
                    "Application layer",
                    "Database layer"
                ],
                "answer": "Application layer"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is BAPI?",
                "options": [
                    "Business Application Programming Interface",
                    "Business Applications Packages and Interfaces",
                    "Business Applications Programs and Information"
                ],
                "answer": "Business Application Programming Interface"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "Which one of the following signs should Local Package name start with?",
                "options": [
                    "#",
                    "*",
                    "$",
                    "@"
                ],
                "answer": "$"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "What is TMG?",
                "options": [
                    "Table Modification and Grouping",
                    "Table Maintenance Generator",
                    "Transportation Management and Guidelines",
                    "Tables, Maps and Graphics"
                ],
                "answer": "Table Maintenance Generator"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "Transaction code for creating, displaying and changing a database table?",
                "options": [
                    "SE24",
                    "SE38",
                    "SE11",
                    "SE93"
                ],
                "answer": "SE11"
            }
        ],
        "difficult": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "How is database access achieved in ADBC (ABAP Database Connectivity)?",
                "options": [
                    "Using Native SQL",
                    "Using Enhanced Open SQL",
                    "Using SQLScript"
                ],
                "answer": "Using Native SQL"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "Which parameters are not allowed in AMDP (ABAP Managed Database Procedures) classes?",
                "options": [
                    "Exporting parameters",
                    "Returning parameters",
                    "Importing parameters",
                    "Changing parameters"
                ],
                "answer": "Returning parameters"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "Which of the following sources can be used for generating ALV IDA (ABAP List Viewer with Integrated Database Access)?",
                "options": [
                    "Database Table",
                    "External View published in ABAP Dictionary",
                    "CDS View",
                    "All of the options"
                ],
                "answer": "All of the options"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "Which component of an application server controls the data traffic between a work process and a presentation server?",
                "options": [
                    "Dispatcher",
                    "SAP GUI",
                    "Front-end processor",
                    "Screen Processor"
                ],
                "answer": "Dispatcher"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "What system command needs to be typed in the command field to start a Debugger?",
                "options": [
                    "/h",
                    "/i",
                    "/n",
                    "/hx"
                ],
                "answer": "/h"
            }
        ],
        "advanced": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "Which Transaction Code is used to customise the standard SAP system?",
                "options": [
                    "SE93",
                    "SWDD",
                    "SPRO",
                    "SE73"
                ],
                "answer": "SPRO"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "You have created a screen with 5 radio buttons. How do you ensure that only one radio button is selected at a time?",
                "options": [
                    "Combine all the radio buttons into a group",
                    "Create a common function code for all the radio buttons",
                    "Assign all the radio buttons to the same modification group",
                    "Enclose all entire radio button in a frame"
                ],
                "answer": "Combine all the radio buttons into a group"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": " What needs to be done to follow the code-to-data approach to programming?",
                "options": [
                    "Transfer all data from the database to the ABAP layer, and then aggregate the results",
                    "Aggregate data on the database, and transfer the results to the ABAP layer",
                    "Perform expensive calculations on the ABAP application server"
                ],
                "answer": "Aggregate data on the database, and transfer the results to the ABAP layer"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "What is the purpose of implicit enhancement points?",
                "options": [
                    "To add fields to an SAP database table",
                    "To add code to a standard SAP program",
                    "To change code in a standard SAP program",
                    "To create a secondary index for an SAP database table"
                ],
                "answer": "To add code to a standard SAP program"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "You have implemented a class CL_CUSTOMER in which you defined a private attribute. From where can you access this attribute directly?",
                "options": [
                    "From all methods of all subclasses of CL_CUSTOMER",
                    "From all methods of the class CL_CUSTOMER",
                    "From any program using the class CL_CUSTOMER"
                ],
                "answer": "From all methods of the class CL_CUSTOMER"
            }
        ]
    }
}